ibid2save.com 2014-04-13

# Privacy Policy - iBid2Save.com

**_Privacy Policy_**

Effective as of April 1, 2011.  
IBID2SAVE.com is a service provided by IBID2SAVE, LLC and iBid2Save Ltd (referred to herein as "IBID2SAVE", "us", and "we").

**OUR PLEDGE**

Our subscribers'privacy is of primary importance to IBID2SAVE. We acknowledge and respect your personal privacy, and this Privacy Policy is intended to describe how we handle your personal information for our services on the IBID2SAVE.com website, any of its related websites, or any related tools, applications, and services provided by IBID2SAVE (collectively referred to herein as "IBID2SAVE.com website". It is very important that our subscribers are fully informed about the use of their personal information prior to their choosing to subscribe to IBID2SAVE.com. Therefore, please read this Privacy Policy carefully before using the IBID2SAVE.com website or submitting any personal information to IBID2SAVE.

**SCOPE**

This Privacy Policy provides detailed information regarding IBID2SAVE’s treatment of all personally identifiable information and other information collected by IBID2SAVE while you are visiting or using the IBID2SAVE.com website. This Privacy Policy applies generally to the IBID2SAVE.com website and content and other related websites where this Privacy Policy appears in the footer of the page.

Please be advised, some related websites operated by IBID2SAVE and third party websites linked to the IBID2SAVE website may be governed by separate privacy policies. The Privacy Policy that applies to any of IBID2SAVE’s domains or subdomains is always that policy that appears in the footer of each such website.

PLEASE READ THE ENTIRE PRIVACY POLICY AND MAKE SURE YOU FULLY UNDERSTAND IBID2SAVE’S POLICIES AND PRACTICES REGARDING THE COLLECTION, STORAGE, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION PRIOR TO COMPLETING THE REGISTRATION PROCESS AND ANY USE OF THE IBID2SAVE.COM WEBSITE.

By accepting this Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions during the registration process, you expressly consent to IBID2SAVE’s policies and practices regarding the collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as specifically described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions. Furthermore, by your continued use of this IBID2SAVE.com website you expressly consent to IBID2SAVE’s ongoing collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions. 

If you do not agree with these practices you are free to discontinue your use of the IBID2SAVE.com website at any time.

Should you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or any of the policies and practices contained therein, please email us at [support@IBID2SAVE.com](mailto:support@IBID2SAVE.com).

**COLLECTION OF DATA**

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

You can browse the IBID2SAVE.com website and our related sites without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. As a normal course of business, IBID2SAVE collects certain aggregate non-personally identifiable information when anyone visits the IBID2SAVE.com website or any of its related sites to browse, read or download information. The types of non-personally identifiable information we may collect and store includes the standard computer and connection information that your browser sends to every website such as IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring website addresses; statistics on page views; traffic to and from the IBID2SAVE website and its related sites, advertisement data; and standard web log information and information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data. The non-personally identifiable information IBID2SAVE collects and stores does not reveal the specific identity of the individual user, and it does not relate to a single identifiable visitor. Furthermore, we generally do not link any non-personally identifiable information to anything that will allow us to identify specific users unless it is necessary to enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, users or others. 

The purpose of collecting such non-personally identifiable information is that it tells IBID2SAVE such things as how many users have visited the sites and which pages are commonly accessed its visitors. By collecting this information, IBID2SAVE can more effectively tailor the IBID2SAVE.com website and our other sites to create a better experience for our visitors.

IBID2SAVE also may collect aggregate and non-personal information through "cookies" or "web beacons" as explained below in more detail. IBID2SAVE collects and reports aggregate statistical information on the open rates and response rates generated by the email campaigns we send. We also collect this information through the use of technologies such as "cookies", "web beacons" and "IP addresses", which are discussed in greater detail below. We collect this information in order to determine what types of advertisements are of interest to list members and to enhance the IBID2SAVE experience. We may also group this information into aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the IBID2SAVE.com website to our existing or potential users or other third parties, or in response to a government request. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you, other users or any other visitors to the IBID2SAVE.com website.

Personally Identifiable Information

Please be advised, once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. In order to actively participate on the IBID2SAVE.com website or its related sites, you are required to provide us with certain Personally Identifiable Information ("Personal Information"). By providing us with your personal information, you are expressly consenting to IBID2SAVE’s ongoing collection, use, and disclosure of such personal information and transfer and storage of that personal information on our servers located in the United States.

When you register to be a subscriber or user of the IBID2SAVE.com website, IBID2SAVE collects and stores the following Personal Information:

  * email address, first and last name, phone number, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;
  * transactional information based on your activities on the sites (such as bidding, buying, selling, item and content you generate or that relates to your account);
  * shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item;
  * community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through our sites, and correspondence sent to us;
  * other information from your interaction with our sites, services, content and advertising, including device ID, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information;
  * additional information we ask you to submit to authenticate yourself or if we believe you are violating site policies (for example, we may ask you to send us an ID or bill to verify your address, or to answer additional questions online to help verify your identity);
  * information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data;
  * other supplemental information from third parties (for example, if you incur a debt to IBID2SAVE, we will generally conduct a credit check by obtaining additional information about you from a credit bureau, as permitted by law).

PLEASE NOTE: This Privacy Policy does not protect you when you send information, ideas, concepts or inventions to us by email, or to the various departments listed on the IBID2SAVE.com website.

**MARKETING OF DATA TO THIRD PARTIES**

IBID2SAVE does not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in any of our ad-customization programs, you will be able to do so through your preferences listed under the "My Account" page or by following the directions provided with the communication or advertisement itself.

**USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION DATA**

IBID2SAVE's purpose for collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience. By registering as a subscriber or user of IBID2SAVE, you expressly consent that we may use your PERSONAL INFORMATION to:

  * Provide the services and customer support you request;
  * Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * Prevent, detect, and investigate potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms & Conditions;
  * Customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising;
  * Inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotions related to IBID2SAVE or services or products available on the IBID2SAVE.com website and other third party services and products, targeted marketing, and promotions which IBID2SAVE believe you may have an interest in based on your use of the IBID2SAVE.com website or other information you have provided to IBID2SAVE or other third parties;
  * Compare information and verify it with third parties for accuracy;
  * Send autodialed and prerecorded messages regarding transactions and fee collections to the telephone numbers (including wireless and cellular) you have provided us;
  * Other uses as described when we collect the information.

**REGISTRATION AND SHARING THROUGH THIRD PARTY SERVICES**

IBID2SAVE may offer single sign-on services that allow you to use third party login credentials to sign into the IBID2SAVE.com website. With your permission, IBID2SAVE may also transfer to IBID2SAVE certain profile information contained in your third-party profile. IBID2SAVE may also, for your use, enable you to import information about who you are connected to, as well as enable you to share information with those third-party sites. If you wish to discontinue such sharing, you will be able to do so through your preference page.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

IBID2SAVE may disclose your Personal Information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

IBID2SAVE may also share your Personal Information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity.

  * IBID2SAVE’s related entities in order to provide joint content and services (like registration, transactions and customer support), to help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and violations of our policies, and to guide decisions about their products, services and communications. Such related entities will use this information to send you marketing communications only if you’ve requested their services.
  * Service providers who assist us with our marketing efforts, business operations, and other communications (i.e., fraud investigations, bill collection, and affiliate and rewards programs, but those service providers will not use this Personal Information for their own marketing purposes and are prohibited by contract from sharing this PERSONAL INFORMATION with any party other than IBID2SAVE.
  * Other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service).
  * Law enforcement, governmental agencies, or authorized third-parties in the following limited circumstances: (1) upon receipt of a properly authorized and authenticated governmental request for information relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other IBID2SAVE user to legal liability; (2) in response to a subpoena or a court order; (3) to comply with relevant laws; (4) in response to an investigation of fraud regarding a specific individual; (5) in an effort to safeguard the person or property of an IBID2SAVE employee or a third party; or (6) when IBID2SAVE believes in good faith that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect its interests or we believe in good faith that the law requires the sharing of your personal information to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.
  * Other business entities if in the future IBID2SAVE decides to sell, merge or otherwise reorganize its business. IBID2SAVE reserves the right to transfer and disclose Personal Information in this circumstance, but IBID2SAVE will require that such entity be governed by this Privacy Policy as it existed at the time of any such change in business conditions unless you give prior consent to such new privacy policy.

**INFORMATION YOU SHARE ON IBID2SAVE.COM**

Once you have been approved as a registered user with IBID2SAVE, you will be required to choose a user name to identify yourself on the site. This user name will be displayed throughout the IBID2SAVE.com website and therefore provided to the public. Furthermore, this under name is connected to all of your IBID2SAVE activity. Other people visiting or using the IBID2SAVE.com website can see your bids, purchases, feedback, and associated comments, and if you win an auction, IBID2SAVE will automatically display the number of bids and dollar value of those bids when the auction ends. Therefore, if you associate your actual name with your user name, the people to whom you have revealed your name will be able to personally identify your activities on the IBID2SAVE.com website. 

Also note that if you access the IBID2SAVE.com website from a shared computer or a computer in an internet café, certain information about you, such as your user name, activity or reminders from IBID2SAVE, may also be visible to other individuals who use the computer after you. It is your responsibility to ensure that all private information is removed from the public or shared computer should you choose to use one.

PLEASE REMEMBER, ONCE YOU MAKE A PUBLIC POSTIING OF ANY KIND, YOU MAY NOT BE ABLE TO CHANGE OR REMOVE IT.

**PUBLIC FORUMS**

The IBID2SAVE.com website may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its registered users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any of your personal information.

**ACCESS, REVIEW AND CHANGE OF PERSONAL DATA**

You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to the IBID2SAVE.com website at any time. Generally, we will not modify your personal information because it is difficult to verify your identity remotely. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. Accurate information is required for billing and delivery purposes. You are therefore required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or such information is inaccurate.

**"OPT OUT"**

It is just as easy to "opt-out" as it is to "opt-in!" You can choose to remove yourself from our database and terminate your subscription at any time. To "opt-out," simply click the unsubscribe link located with any offer provided by IBID2SAVE . You can also choose to remove yourself from our database at any time by changing your preferences under the My Account page located on the first page of the IBID2SAVE.com website.

**CLOSING YOUR ACCOUNT**

Upon your request, IBID2SAVE will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms & Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

You should be aware that it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us from our servers. The need to back-up our systems to protect information from inadvertent loss means that a copy of your Personal Information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate. Nevertheless, we promise that upon receiving your request, all Personal Information stored in the databases we actively use for research and daily business activities, and other readily searchable media, will be deleted.

**IP ADDRESSES**

An IP address is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the web. Web servers, the computers that "serve" web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. IBID2SAVE collects IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report aggregate information to third parties and to track the use of the IBID2SAVE.com website. When visitors request pages from the IBID2SAVE.com website or click on a link in a email, our servers log the visitors’ IP addresses. We reserve the right to use IP addresses to identify a visitor or user when it will enhance the user’s experience or if we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the IBID2SAVE.com website’s policies or to protect IBID2SAVE, the IBID2SAVE.com website, its visitors, registered users or others.

**USE OF COOKIES**

Cookies are pieces of information that any website may transfer to your browser that are then stored in your computer's system. The IBID2SAVE.com website uses cookies. A "cookie" is a small text file that contains a string of alphanumeric characters. There are two types of cookies that may be used at the IBID2SAVE.com website: a persistent cookie and a session cookie. A persistent cookie gets entered by your Web browser into the "Cookies" folder on your computer and remains in this "Cookies" folder after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. A session cookie is held temporarily in your computer’s memory and disappears after you close your browser or shut off your computer.

Cookies make web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you are at a website. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you’ll find them at most websites. Cookies are returned to the website that deposited them when a visitor returns to that site. Cookies can provide certain information, for example, whether a user is a first-time visitor or has visited the website before and what areas of the website are of greatest interest to the user. 

By showing how and when visitors use the IBID2SAVE.com website, cookies help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Information such as the total number of visitors and pages viewed is most easily tracked with cookies. We may use the information from cookies to make improvements and updates to the IBID2SAVE.com website and to tailor our services to our visitors’ and registered users’ needs. In addition, the deposit of cookies by the IBID2SAVE.com website may enhance your online experience by allowing us to save your preferences for your next visit or controlling the frequency of "pop-up" windows.

If you have arrived at this website by clicking on a banner ad for one of our products or services, a session cookie may be used. This cookie will contain an identification number for the ad that you clicked on, or will contain an identification number for the site that you were visiting when you clicked on the banner ad. This session cookie helps IBID2SAVE’s marketing department determine which of our ads attract the most visitors. If, after you arrive at our site, you choose to request further information from us about our products and services, the personal information that you provide in that request will be linked to the information in the session cookie. This also helps IBID2SAVE’s marketing department measure the effectiveness of our advertising. This "linking" may also be used to target future advertisements to you or to send you emails about future goods and services from IBID2SAVE and goods and services of other third parties. You will receive emails about our products only if you tell us on the product request page that you want us to send them to you. Because this is a session cookie, it will disappear once you have closed your browser. If you return to our site via another one of our ads, you will appear as a new visitor unless and until you provide further personal information. 

You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, please be aware that some features of the IBID2SAVE.com website will not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies.

A few important things you should know about cookies are that:

  * We offer certain features that are available only through the use of cookies. 
  * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status.
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session.
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of some of our sites or services.
  * You may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages of the sites that we do not control. (For example, if you clink on a link to a third party web page, there may be a cookie placed by that web page.)

**WEB BEACONS**

Web beacons, also known as "clear gifs," "one-pixel gifs," "web bugs," "Internet tags" or "pixel tags," are small graphic images on a website or in an e-mail that allow IBID2SAVE and third parties to monitor the activity on our website or to make cookies more effective. We use log files to store the data that is collected through web beacons.

We use a third-party email technology to send emails that you have agreed to receive from both IBID2SAVE and other third parties. Web beacons are used in those email messages to measure the effectiveness of our advertising. If you would like to stop receiving IBID2SAVE’s email publications to which you have subscribed, you may unsubscribe by clinking the link at the bottom of the email or by changing your preferences under the "Your Account" page.

**SECURITY MEASURES**

Your IBID2SAVE account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Therefore your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your IBID2SAVE password to anyone. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. **IBID2SAVE will never ask for your password in an e-mail or over the phone.** If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. In the event you believe your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify IBID2SAVE at support@IBID2SAVE.com and change your password.

Please remember to log out of your IBID2SAVE account and to close your internet browser window whenever you leave the IBID2SAVE.com website; this is especially important if you use a shared computer or a computer in public locations. IBID2SAVE will assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.

IBID2SAVE endeavors to safeguard and protect our users' information. When users submit information on our website, such information is protected both online and offline. The servers in which we store Personal Information are kept in a secure physical environment. IBID2SAVE has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. Currently, IBID2SAVE uses Secure Socket Layer Software ("SSL") to protect data and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, names and addresses as they are transmitted over the internet. Please be advised that, although we take reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, IBID2SAVE cannot warrant that your information will be absolutely secure, but access to your information is strictly limited and not accessible to the public. Any transmission of data at or through the IBID2SAVE.com website is at your own risk.

**PROTECTION FROM WEB CRAWLERS OR SPAM**

IBID2SAVE assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms & Conditions. We will not rent, lease or sell your e-mail address to third parties if you have chosen to "opt out" of such marketing programs. Furthermore, we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please email us at support@IBID2SAVE.com immediately.

**RIGHT TO CONTACT VIA TELEPHONE**

By registering at the IBID2SAVE.com website, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (referred to herein as the "Rule") and other telemarketing laws such as FCC rules. Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, we reserve the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the Rule.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Occasionally, at our discretion, IBID2SAVE may include or offer third party products or services on our website or through email marketing campaigns. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, IBID2SAVE seeks to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**CHILDREN**

IBID2SAVE is sensitive to the need to protect the privacy of children who use the internet. IBID2SAVE does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under the age of eighteen (18) consistent with and exceeding the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). If we discover or are otherwise notified that we have received any such information from a child in violation of this policy, we will delete that information. If you are under the age of eighteen (18), please do not attempt to provide any personally identifiable information on the IBID2SAVE.com website. If you believe for any reason that IBID2SAVE has any information from or about a child under the age of thirteen, please contact us immediately by clicking on "Contact Us" and sending us an e-mail and we will take appropriate steps to remove such information from our files.

Please review the privacy policy of other sites you or your children elect to link to through the IBID2SAVE.com website for the children's privacy policy of those sites. IBID2SAVE is not responsible for the privacy policy or other content of any other website, including sites that are co-branded.

**NOTICE OF PRIVACY RIGHTS TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

California law requires that we provide you with a summary of your privacy rights under the California Online Privacy Protection Act (the "Act") and the California Business and Professions Code. As required by the Act, California residents who have provided Personal Information to IBID2SAVE are disclosed the categories of personally identifiable information that we collect through this website and the categories of third party persons or entities with whom such personally identifiable information may be shared for direct marketing purposes at their request. California law requires us to inform California residents, at their request, (1) the categories of personally identifiable information we collect and what third parties we share that information with; (2) the names and addresses of those third parties; and (3) examples of the products marketed by those companies. 

The Act further requires us to allow California residents to control who you do not want us to share that information with. To obtain this information, please send a request by email or standard mail to the address found below. When contacting us, please indicate your name, address, email address, and what personally identifiable information you do not want us to share with third parties. The request should be sent to the attention of our legal department, and labeled "California Customer Choice Notice." This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. IBID2SAVE reserves the right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this section. Please allow thirty (30) days for a response. Also, please note that there is no charge for controlling the sharing of your personally identifiable information or requesting this notice.

If you have any questions about your California privacy rights or this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@IBID2SAVE.com](mailto:support@IBID2SAVE.com) or in writing at:

IBID2SAVE, LLC  
Customer Service Department  
Attn: California Customer Choice Notice  
2820 Selwyn Avenue  
Unit 415  
Charlotte, NC 28209

**TERMS & CONDITIONS**

Please also visit our Terms & Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our IBID2SAVE.com website.

**GENERAL**

IBID2SAVE may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the new Privacy Policy on the IBID2SAVE.com website. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the IBID2SAVE.com website. You will also be notified of any amendment of this Privacy Policy by email or at the time you log into the IBID2SAVE.com website. However, IBID2SAVE reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. Consequently, you should review this Privacy Policy for changes each time you visit the IBID2SAVE.com website.

If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy or any revised policy, please exit the IBID2SAVE.com website immediately. This website and the servers that make this website available are located in the United States. By using the IBID2SAVE.com website you expressly agree to the transfer, collection, processing and use of data by the IBID2SAVE.com website as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

**QUESTIONS?**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the IBID2SAVE.com website, or your dealings with the IBID2SAVE.com website that are not otherwise answered online, please email us at support@IBID2SAVE.com.

Written correspondence may also be sent to:  
IBID2SAVE, LLC  
Attn: Customer Service Department  
2820 Selwyn Avenue  
Unit 415  
Charlotte, NC 28209
